Email: me@kitsonkelly.com Mobile: +44 (0) 7831 591 913

Curriculum Vitae

Director of Technology/CTO

Experienced leader who delivers technology management that meets the needs of the business. Focus on delivering solutions that solve business problems effectively. Recently experienced in leading edge OTT media operators as well as having a background in business-to-business and large-scale contact centre technology.

Professional Strengths

- Strong and diverse technical experience
- Experience with diverse sourcing models
- Direct, forthright and accountable
- Capable business acumen with understanding from marketing, sales, operations, innovation and delivery
- Able to identify and grow talent

Professional Experience

Head of Technology; NOW TV; London, UK

Sep. 2013 - Present

Lead technology for the fastest growing OTT video streaming service in the UK. As part of Sky Plc., NOW TV has gained success in getting non-pay TV customers to pay for TV. Having the biggest and best pay TV content in the UK has meant that NOW TV has had to have a diverse distribution as well as the ability to meet the scalability demands of the customers.

- Oversaw an over 10 fold increase in customers
- Responsible for the whole gamut of technology, from client application to customer management systems, to eCommerce
- Led teams innovating in solving technology challenges that had never been encountered before
- Launched clients on new eight devices
- Enabled delivery of consumer electronic devices via online and through a retail supply chain
- Directly responsible for a department of 110 and over £10m annual budget

Kitson P. Kelly Curriculum Vitae

Head of Technology; Sky Business; Livingston, UK

May 2010 - Aug. 2013

Lead technology fort the business-to-business division of Sky, supplying Sky and The Cloud WiFi to tens of thousands of locations across the UK and ROI.

- Delivered the multi-million pound CRM replacement programme
- Integrated the Cloud WiFi provisioning and management into CRM systems
- Transitioned from 160 contact-led department delivering a programme to a 70 person efficient perm BAU department over 2 years

Director; Asseverate Services Ltd; London, UK

Oct. 2009 - May 2010

An independent contractor, focusing on call centre technology. Led the technical architecture and operations activities to stabilise the contact centre technology for a large client while assisting in charting a course to return the solution to BAU operations.

Practice Solution Architect; Dimension Data; London, UK

Dec. 2006 - Oct. 2009

Led architecture and solution design for engagements in the UK around call centre technology. Focused on large-scale VoIP contact centres and self-service speech recognition technology.

- Architected the largest VoIP contact centre at the time around 7k users over 8 locations
- Provided thought leadership and consulting in contact centre technology in Europe, South Africa and Australia in addition to the UK
- Architected and led delivery of a speech-recognition voice self service solution
- Led technical conversations between Cisco and Genesys about integration of their VoIP products

Senior Principal Consultant; eLoyalty; Lake Forest, IL, USA

Jan. 1998 - Sept. 2006

Consultant and architect providing services in the call centre technology arena. Focused on large scale, global solutions for large enterprises.

- Assignments globally, including Hong Kong, Germany, Ireland, UK and France
- Led relationship for key suppliers and vendors
- Clients in media, insurance, finance, healthcare, communications and service sectors

Previous Roles Upon Request

Kitson P. Kelly Curriculum Vitae

Education

High School Diploma - Cactus High School - Glendale, AZ, USA - 1987-1991 Some Courses/Non-Degree - Glendale Community College - Glendale, AZ, USA - 1992-1993

Contributions/Recognition/Training

- Contributor and Committer to the Dojo Toolkit (Committer since April 2012)
- Contributor to other open source projects including The Intern Testing Framework
- Presented at various industry conferences for professionally and for work on Dojo Toolkit